是那个男人的"婚前兄弟礼"
His... bro mitzvah!
bro mitzvah婚前兄弟礼是bar mitzvah犹太成年礼的改编
你才不是刚想到的
You didn't just think of that.
你这几个月来一直在念叨这事
You've been saying it for months every...
但我有点进退两难
But here's my dilemma:
我普通晚上过得跟普通人的单身派对一样
my average night is like an average guy's bachelor party.
所以不要见怪  如果你俩真的在策划
So, no offense, but if you two plan it,
那肯定是平淡到  干嘛要等  极点
it's gonna be ordi-- why wait for it?-- nary.
平淡无奇
Ordinary.
我可以帮忙啊
I can help.
你吗
You?
你看起来是个好孩子
Look, you seem like a nice kid,
但兄弟的未婚妻
but bros' fiancee
不能帮忙策划单身派对
cannot plan bachelor parties.
抱歉  你们俩得自食其力
Sorry. You two are on your own.
你们肯定会让我失望的
And you will disappoint me.
但记得让我失望得高兴点  好吗
But make it great, okay?
但这是一个很棒的开头
But this is a strong start.